Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Commercial Recordings Collection AIA.031.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: 78 RPM Records, circa 1903-1959; 2734 sound discs
  - Side A: Taylor Trio, "Mother Machree" [45622] Side B: Taylor Trio, "Because" [45623] (Columbia A1735) (Disk XA78 431)
  - Side A: Taylor Trio, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charm" [46372] Side B: Taylor Trio, "Ben Bolt" [46373] (Columbia A1959) (Disk XA78 1799)
  - Side A: Taylor Trio, "Old Black Joe" [45873] Side B: Stehl, De Jaeger and Weinstein, "Perfect Day" [45891] (Columbia A1809) (Disk XA78 2142)
  - Side A: Tempo Skating Band with Lloyd Sullivan, "Irish Washer Woman" [AM 2152] Side B: Tempo Skating Band with Lloyd Sullivan, "El Manisero" [AM 2153] (Tempo TR 768) (Disk XA78 432)
  - Side A: Terrell, John, "Mick Who Threw the Brick" [One-sided]" (Zon-O-Phone I 9668) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2661)
  - Side A: Terry, Gene, "Ballymaquilty Band" [E3-FB-0313] Side B: Terry, Gene, "Hannigan's Hooley" [E3-FB-0316] (RCA Victor 20-5211) (Disk XA78 2605)
  - Side A: Terry (The Irish Minstrel), "Isle of Innisfree" [OEA.14564] Side B: Terry (The Irish Minstrel), "There's a Little Bit of Irish " [OEA.14565] (His Master's Voice I.P.576) (Disk XA78 433)
  - Side A: Terry (The Irish Minstrel), "Peggy O'Donovan" [OEA.14506-1] Side B: Terry (The Irish Minstrel), "My Way" [OEA.14507-1] (His Master's Voice I.P.588) (Disk XA78 434)
  - Side A: Terry Lane's Ceildhe Band, "Set Dance" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Terry Lane's Ceildhe Band, "Foley's Hotel" [Matrix # not listed] (Irish I.R.1014) (Disk XA78 947)
  - Side A: Terry, Gene, "You'll Never Forget About Ireland" [E3FB-0309] Side B: Terry, Gene, "Ballymaquilty Band" [E3FB-0313] (RCA Victor 26-7525) (Disk XA78 453)
  - Side A: Terry, Gene, "Bally Maquilty Band" [E3-FB-0313] Side B: Terry, Gene, "Hanigan's Hooley" [E3-FB-0316] (RCA Victor 20-5211) (Disk XA78 1237)
  - Side A: Texas Jim Robertson, "Sweet Baby" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Texas Jim Robertson, "Miz O'Reilly's Daughter" [Matrix # not listed] (Bluebird 33-0503) (Disk XA78 393)
  - Side A: Teyte, Maggie, "Oft in the Stilly Night" [OEA.9524] Side B: Teyte, Maggie, "Comin' Thro' the Rye" [OEA.9525] (His Master's Voice I.R.227) (Disk XA78 454)
  - Side A: Teyte, Maggie, "My Ain Folk" [6574] Side B: Teyte, Maggie, "Believe Me All those Endearing Young Charms" [6597] (Edison 82163) (Disk XA78 1800)
  - Side A: Thebom, Blanche, "Dear Little Boy of Mine" [] Side B: Thebom, Blanche, "I'll Forget You" [] (Victor 10-1139-B) (Disk XA78 2512)
  - Side A: Thebom, Blanche, "Mother Machree" [] Side B: Thebom, Blanche, "Love Me and the World is Mine" [] (Victor 10-1138-B) (Disk XA78 2511)
  - Side A: Thomas, Thomas L., "Danny Boy" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Thomas, Thomas L., "Flow Gently Sweet Afton" [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 10-1312) (Disk XA78 2036)
  - Side A: Thomas, Thomas L., "Rhyfelgyrch Gwyr Harlech" [OA.071972] Side B: Thomas, Thomas L., "Ar Hyd Y Nos" [OA.071970] ( B.10207) (Disk XA78 2350)
  - Side A: Thomas, William, "Old Bog Road" [A.9066] Side B: Thomas, William, "Slievenamon" [A.9067] (Regal Zonophone IZ.572) (Disk XA78 455)
  - Side A: Thomas, William, "Wearing of the Green" [28003] Side B: Thomas, William, "Daughters of Erin" [39709] (Columbia A1676) (Disk XA78 456)
  - Side A: Thomas, William, "Barney O'Hea" [28287] Side B: Anderson, Archie, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [28333] (Columbia A1447) (Disk XA78 1257)
  - Side A: Thompson, Bill with Hubert Greenslade, "Queen of Connemara" [OEL.429] Side B: Thompson, Bill with Hubert Greenslade, "On the Banks of My Own Lovely Lee" [OEL.433] (His Master's Voice I.M.1462) (Disk XA78 1811)
  - Side A: Thompson, Bill with Hubert Greenslade, "Mountains of Pomeroy" [OEL.431-1] Side B: Thompson, Bill with Hubert Greenslade, "Boolavogue" [OEL.434-1] (His Master's Voice I.M.1460) (Disk XA78 1817)
  - Side A: Thompson, Geo. L, "Cohen on the Telephone" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Jones, Ada, "If I Knock the "L" Out of Kelly" [Matrix # not listed] (Rex 5370) (Disk XA78 1812)
  - Side A: Thornton and Earls, "Old Boreen" [GB.4274] Side B: Thornton and Earls, "Maid of Mullingar" [GB.4279] (Decca F.2974) (Disk XA78 1813)
  - Side A: Thornton and Earls, "Molly Branigan" [CE.6132] Side B: Thornton and Earls, "Eileen Oge" [CE.6133] (Regal Zonophone IZ.543) (Disk XA78 1814)
  - Side A: Thornton and Earls, "Come Back to Paddy Reilly, to Ballyjamesduff" [CAL.105] Side B: Thornton and Earls, "Little Nellie Cassidy" [CAL.106] (Regal Zonophone IZ.863) (Disk XA78 1815)
  - Side A: Thorpe, Leslie, "Shetland Reels" [M669A] Side B: Thorpe, Leslie, "Flowers of Edinburgh" [M670B] (Beltona BL.2327) (Disk XA78 1816)
  - Side A: Thunder Brothers and Albert Healy, "Tipperary Christening" [CAL.335] Side B: Thunder Brothers and Albert Healy, "Ballymaquilty" [CAL.387] (Regal Zonophone IZ.1300) (Disk XA78 936)
  - Side A: Tibbett, Lawrence, "Drink to Me Only With Thine Eyes" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Tibbett, Lawrence, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms" [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 1238) (Disk XA78 98)
  - Side A: Tibbett, Lawrence, "Drink to Me Only with Thine Eyes" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Tibbett, Lawrence, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 1238) (Disk XA78 2030)
  - Side A: Tibbett, Lawrence, "Last Night When We Were Young" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Tibbett, Lawrence, "On the Road to Mandalay" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 11877) 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2261)
  - Side A: Tietge Sisters, "There's No One Like My Mother to Me" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Tietge Sisters, "My Wild Irish Rose" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 20189) (Disk XA78 1235)
  - Side A: Tobin, Michael, "Molly Brannigan" [3917] Side B: Tobin, Michael, "Kitty of Coleraine" [3918] (Capitol 10196) (Disk XA78 99)
  - Side A: Tobin, Michael, "Rory O'Moore" [3918] Side B: Tobin, Michael, "Mother Machree" [3919] (Capitol 10197) (Disk XA78 926)
  - Side A: Todd, Dick, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Todd, Dick, "Write a Letter to Your Mother" [Matrix # not listed] (Bluebird B-10697) (Disk XA78 1908)
  - Side A: Todd, Peter, "If You're Irish Come Into the Parlor" [12311] Side B: Todd, Peter, "tell Ya Momma" [12309] (Coral 60111) (Disk XA78 2716)
  - Tommy Drennan and the Monarchs, "50 Years After", undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Side A: Touhey, Patrick J., "Drowsy Maggie" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Clancy, Patrick J. and Arthur P. Kenna, "Dublin Jig Medley" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18639) (Disk XA78 945)
  - Side A: Tracy, Dan, "Wee Melodeon" [OEL.367] Side B: Tracy, Dan, "Kate from Ballymore" [OEL.368] (His Master's Voice I.M.1111) (Disk XA78 933)
  - Side A: Tracy, Dan, "Pat of Mullincar" [OEL.366] Side B: Tracy, Dan, "Grand Hotel in Castlebar" [OEL.369] (His Master's Voice I.M.1112) (Disk XA78 934)
  - Side A: Tracy, Dan, "My Irish Fairy" [OEL.372] Side B: Tracy, Dan, "Country Jaunt" [OEL.371] (His Master's Voice I.M.1128) (Disk XA78 944)
  - Side A: Tremain, George, "North Skelton and Boosbeck Long Sword Dances Part 1" [OEA.11543] Side B: Tremain, George, "North Skelton and Boosbeck Long Sword Dances Part 2" [OEA.11544] (His Master's Voice B.9539) (Disk XA78 1805)
  - Side A: Trinity Choir, "Joy to the World!" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Trinity Choir, "Oh Come, All Ye Faithful " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 20246) (Disk XA78 943)
  - Side A: Troubadours, "Popular Songs of Yesterday-Medley Waltz No.1" [] Side B: Troubadours, "Popular Songs of Yesterday-Medley Waltz No.2" [] (Victor 35831-B) (Disk XA78 2515)
  - Side A: Trumbauer, Frankie, "Wearing of the Green & the Irish Washerwoman" [US 1401] Side B: Trumbauer, Frankie, "No Retard" [US 1402] (Varsity 8215) (Disk XA78 2595)
  - Side A: Tucker, Tommy, "I'm Praying to Saint Christopher" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Tucker, Tommy, "Cherry Stones" [Matrix # not listed] (MGM 10767) (Disk XA78 942)
  - Side A: Turk Murphy's Jazz Band, "Irish Black Bottom" [LK 145-3] Side B: Turk Murphy's Jazz Band, "Darktown Strutters Ball" [LK-144-4] (Good Time Jazz 17) (Disk XA78 2386)
  - Side A: Turner, Alan, "How Can I Forget" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Burr, Henry, "Just as Your Mother Was" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18352) (Disk XA78 1224)
  - Side A: Turner, Alan, "Thyere's a Green Hill Out in Flanders" [Not Listed] Side B: Peerless Quartet, "Say a Prayer for the Boys Out There" [Not Listed] (Victor 18411-B) (Disk XA78 2353)
  - Side A: Turner, Alan, "Kathleen Mavourneen" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Hayden Quartet, "Tenting on the Old Camp Ground" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 16404) (Disk XA78 2092)
  - Side A: Tyrone Pipers' Band, "Minstrel Boy" [68567] Side B: Tyrone Pipers' Band, "Wearing of the Green" [68570] (Decca 12249) (Disk XA78 941)
  - Irish Marches, Strathspeys and Reels Played on the Irish War Pipes Tyrone Pipers' Band Side A: "Leaving Glen Urquhart" [68572] Side B: "Major Normon Orr Ewing" [68568] (Decca 12248) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2169)
  - Irish Marches, Strathspeys and Reels Played on the Irish War Pipes Tyrone Pipers' Band Side A: "Minstrel Boy" [68567] Side B: "Wearing of the Green" [68570] (Decca 12249) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2170)
  - Irish Marches, Strathspeys and Reels Played on the Irish War Pipes Tyrone Pipers' Band Side A: "Farewell to Ballinascorney" [68571] Side B: "Men of the West" [68569] (Decca 12250) 78 Set (Disk XA78 2171)
  - Side A: Ulster Amateur Flute Band, "Irish Melodies" [GB. 4179] Side B: Ulster Amateur Flute Band, "Irish Melodies" [GB. 4180] (Rex 15014) (Disk XA78 940)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Adele" [] Side B: Not Listed, "Dreaming" [] (Edison Not Listed) (Disk XA78 2486)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Along the Rocky Road to Dublin" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2645)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Along the Rocky Road to Dublin" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2646)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Arrah! Go On I'm Gonna Go Back to Oregon" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 356) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2653)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 105) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2647)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 105) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2648)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Dancing 'Neath the Irish Moon" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 165) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2654)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Dancing 'Neath the Irish Moon" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 165) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2655)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Dingle Dangle" [] Side B: Not Listed, "I Wish I Was" [] (Edison Not Listed) (Disk XA78 2485)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Fantasie on Irish Airs [One-sided]" [6] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2318)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Flanagan on a Broadway Car Talking" [3621] Side B: Unlisted, "I'm Keeping My Love Lamp Burning For You " [3592] (Harmony Disc A467) (Disk XA78 2358)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Harp That Once Through Tara's Halls" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 277) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2649)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Harp That Once Through Tara's Halls" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 277) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2650)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Imitation of an Irish Comedian" [One-sided]" (Columbia 662) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2688)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "I'm On My Way to Dublin Bay" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 159) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2629)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Ireland Must be Heaven" [One-sided]" (Silvertone 46905) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2699)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Irish Blood" [4270] Side B: Unlisted, "I'm Glad I'm a Boy" [4176] (United A782 ) (Disk XA78 2673)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Irish Medley Jig" [One-sided]" (Columbia 499) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2667)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "It's a Long, Long Way to Tipperary" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 56) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2631)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Jerry Murphy is a Friend of Mine" [One-sided]" (Columbia 939) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2733)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Killarney" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 106) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2642)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Killarney" [One-sided]" (Columbia 14) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2732)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Medley of Irish Airs" [One-sided]" (Columbia 428) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2663)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Medley of Irish Airs" [One-sided]" (Oxford 428) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2662)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Medley of Old Time Songs [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2320)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Mother" [One-sided]" (Emerson 540) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2657)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Mother Machree" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 981) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2731)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "My Wild Irish Rose" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2638)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "My Wild Irish Rose" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2639)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "My Wild Irish Rose" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2640)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "My Wild Irish Rose" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2641)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "My Wild Irish Rose" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 109) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2644)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Nigger Fever" [500] Side B: D'Almaine, Chas., "Imitation of Bagpipes and Scotch Airs" [1532] (United A214) (Disk XA78 2357)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "On the Banks of the Brandywine" [] Side B: Not Listed, "I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen" [] (Edison Not Listed) (Disk XA78 2487)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "O Sole Mio" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 1022) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2643)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Preacher and the Bear [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2361)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Scots Wha Hae Wi' Wallace Bled" [3228] Side B: Unlisted, "Little Boy Called Taps" [3225] (Harmony Disc A458) (Disk XA78 2359)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "She's the Daughter of Mother Machree" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 374) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 374)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "She's the Daughter of Mother Machree" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 374) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2637)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Special Demonstration Double-Disc" [] Side B: Columbia Male Quartette, "Special Demonstration Double-Disc" [] (Columbia Not listed) (Disk XA78 2384)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Stephen Foster Melodies" [PS 1057] Side B: Not Listed, "Old-Time Favorites" [PS 706] (Philharmonic FR 115-B) (Disk XA78 2516)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Stephen Foster Melodies" [PS 1056] Side B: Not Listed, "Old-Time Favorites" [PS 707] (Philharmonic FR 114-B) (Disk XA78 2517)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "That Tumble Down Shack in Athlone" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 1128) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2633)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "That Tumble Down Shack in Athlone" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 1128) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2634)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "That Tumble Down Shack in Athlone" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 1128) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2635)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "That's What Ireland Means to Me" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 750) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2652)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Till We Meet Again" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 1065) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2651)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Tip Top Tipperary Mary" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 93) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2630)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Wedding of the Irish and the Scotch" [One-sided]" (Emerson 544) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2665)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Wedding of the Irish and the Scotch" [One-sided]" (Emerson 544) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2666)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "When I Dream of Old Erin I'm Dreaming of You" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 161) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2632)
  - Side A: Unlisted, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [One-sided]" (Little Wonder 108) Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2656)
  - Side A: Valentine, Hubert, "Macushla" [OEA.4858] Side B: Valentine, Hubert, "Little Shawl of Blue" [OEA.4860] (His Master's Voice I.M.467) (Disk XA78 354)
  - Side A: Valentine, Hubert, "My Mary of the Curling Hair" [OEA. 6249] Side B: Valentine, Hubert, "Rose of Killarney" [OEA.6250] (His Master's Voice I.M.503) (Disk XA78 355)
  - Side A: Valentine, Hubert, "Bard of Armagh" [OEA.4861] Side B: Valentine, Hubert, "Irish Emigrant" [OEA.4862] (His Master's Voice I.M.465) (Disk XA78 1803)
  - Side A: Valentine, Hubert, "Shannon River" [OEA.6251-2] Side B: Valentine, Hubert, "Because I Love You So Machree" [OEA.6252-2] (His Master's Voice I.M.640) (Disk XA78 1804)
  - Side A: Vallee, Rudy and His Connecticut Yankees, "You're Driving Me Crazy!" [] Side B: Vallee, Rudy and His Connecticut Yankees, "Thinking of You, Dear" [] (Victor 22572-B) (Disk XA78 2312)
  - Side A: Vallely, Father, "Father Vallely's Jubilee Sermon Part I" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Vallely, Father, "Father Vallely's Jubilee Sermon Part II" [Matrix # not listed] (Wilcox-Gay Recordio Catalog # not listed) Non-commercial (Disk XA78 337)
  - Side A: Van and Schenck, "After You Get What You Want You Don't Want It" [79129] Side B: Van and Schenck, "You Tell 'Em" [79306] (Columbia A2966) (Disk XA78 2613)
  - Side A: Van and Schenck, "Huckleberry Finn" [] Side B: Van and Schenck, "Mulberry Rose" [] (Victor 18318-B) (Disk XA78 2460)
  - Side A: Van and Schenck, "I Always Think I'm Up in Heaven" [78023] Side B: Van and Schenck, "Why Do They Call Them Babies?" [78084] (Columbia A2674) (Disk XA78 938)
  - Side A: Van and Schenck, "In the Old Town Hall" [79957] Side B: Van and Schenck, "What's a Gonna Be Next" [79959] (Columbia A3461) (Disk XA78 1808)
  - Side A: Van and Schenck, "O'Reilly " [80004] Side B: Van and Schenck, "Who's Been Around?" [80009] (Columbia A3490) (Disk XA78 2090)
  - Side A: Van and Schenck, "Yaddie Kaddie Kiddie Kaddie Koo" [] Side B: Van and Schenck, "That's How You Can Tell They're Irish" [] (Victor 18220-B) (Disk XA78 2443, Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "As Long as the Shamrock Grows Green " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 60050) One-Sided (Disk XA78 540)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter J., "As Long as the Shamrock Grows Green" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Peerless Quartet, "Wee Little Drop o' the Cruiskeen Lawn" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17148) (Disk XA78 1820)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "Ireland Must Be Heaven for My Mother Came from There" [4948] Side B: Kaufman, Irving, "It's Always Orange Day in California" [4954] (Edison 50396) (Disk XA78 1810)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "Keep Away From the Fellow Who Owns an Automobile " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64181) One-Sided (Disk XA78 2034)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "My Wild Irish Rose" [4168] Side B: Van Brunt, Walter, "Mother Machree" [3764] (Edison 80293) (Disk XA78 1919)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "My Wild Irish Rose" [4168] Side B: Van Brunt, Walter, "Mother Machree" [3764] (Edison 80293) (Disk XA78 2091)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "When I Dream of Old Erin" [38888] Side B: Burr, Henry and Edgar Stoddard, "There's a Girl in the Heart of Maryland" [38921] (Columbia A1360), 1913 (Disk XA78 1982)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "When I Dream of Old Erin" [38888] Side B: Van Brunt, Walter, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [4358] (Columbia 33025-F) (Disk XA78 2539)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [4223] Side B: Van Brunt, Walter, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [3350] (Edison 80255) (Disk XA78 937)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [4223] Side B: Van Brunt, Walter, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [3350] (Edison 80255) (Disk XA78 946)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter, "Yaaka Hula Kickey Dula" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Collins and Harlan, "On the Hoko Moko Isle" [Matrix # not listed] (Edison 50348) (Disk XA78 1096)
  - Side A: Van Brunt, Walter J. and Maurice Burkhardt, "Funny Little Melody" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Murray, Billy, "You May Be Irish, Murphy, But I Think That You're in Dutch" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17213) (Disk XA78 1920)
  - Side A: Van Eps Banjo Orchestra, "I Want to Go Back to Michigan" [39573] Side B: Van Eps Banjo Orchestra, "Soup to Nuts" [39574] (Columbia A1629) (Disk XA78 2482)
  - Side A: Van Eps, Fred, "Black Diamond Rag" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Reitz, Williams H., "Irish and Scotch Melodies" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17168) (Disk XA78 541)
  - Side A: Van Eps, Fred, "Smiler Rag" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Pathe Dance Orchestra, "Blame it On the Blues" [Matrix # not listed] (Pathé 10052) (Disk XA78 2706)
  - Side A: Van Eps Quartet, "So Long Oo-long " [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Joseph's C. Smith's Orchestra, "Lovely Summertime" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18681) (Disk XA78 502)
  - Side A: Van Eps Trio, "Ching Chong - One-Step" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Harold Veo's Orchestra, "Wait Till the Cows Come Home " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18404-B) (Disk XA78 2125)
  - Side A: Van Eps Trio, "Oh, Susie, Behave" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Van Eps Trio, "Monte Cristo, Jr." [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18556) (Disk XA78 1821)
  - Side A: Van Eps Trio, "Where the Lanterns Glow" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Van Eps Trio, "Taxi" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18640) (Disk XA78 503)
  - Side A: Van Gordon, Cyrena, "Irish Love Song" [79924] Side B: Van Gordon, Cyrena, "My Laddie" [79925] (Columbia A3617) (Disk XA78 518)
  - Side A: Venetian Instrumental Quartet, "Kathleen Mavourneen" [4238] Side B: Venetian Instrumental Quartet, "Sweet Spirit, Hear My Prayer" [3837] (Edison 82032) (Disk XA78 1819)
  - Side A: Venetian Instrumental Quartet, "Quanto io t'amo" [5618] Side B: Venetian Instrumental Quartet, "I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen" [5450] (Edison 80391) (Disk XA78 1921)
  - Side A: Venetian Trio, "Humoresque " [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Venetian Trio, "Berceuse from "Jocelyn"" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17454-B) (Disk XA78 2144)
  - Side A: Veo, Harold, "Irish Jigs" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Veo, Harold, "Medley of Irish Reels, No.6" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18308) (Disk XA78 2033)
  - Side A: Veo, Harold, "Reilly's Reel – Medley of Reels" [6121] Side B: Fitzpatrick, Patrick, "Medley of Irish Jigs" [5286] (Edison 50615) (Disk XA78 2104)
  - Side A: Verlet, Alice, "Bonnie, Sweet Bessie" [] Side B: Verlet, Alice, "Comin' Thro' the Rye" [] (Edison Not Listed) (Disk XA78 2479)
  - Side A: Victor Band, "Irish Lilt " [45227] Side B: Victor Band, "Highland Schottische/Highland Fling" [45228] (RCA Victor 21616) (Disk XA78 519)
  - Side A: Victor Band, "Irish Lilt" [45227] Side B: Victor Band, "Highland Schottishe" [45228] (Victor 21616) (Disk XA78 1818)
  - Side A: Victor Band, "Old Zip Coon" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Victor Band, "Lady of the Lake" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 18356-B) (Disk XA78 2145)
  - Side A: Victor Chapel Choir, "We Three Kings of Orient Are" [P 96-3] Side B: Victor Chapel Choir, "Away in a Manger" [P 96-4] (Victor 27645) (Disk XA78 520)
  - Side A: Victor Chapel Choir, "O, Holy Night" [P 96-7] Side B: Victor Chapel Choir, "Nazareth" [P 96-8] (Victor 27647) (Disk XA78 747)
  - Side A: Victor Chapel Choir, "Star of Bethlehem" [P 96-5] Side B: Victor Chapel Choir, "Star of the East" [P 96-6] (Victor 27646) (Disk XA78 969)
  - Side A: Victor Concert Orchestra, "Shepard's Hey" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Victor Concert Orchestra, "Country Gardens" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 20802) (Disk XA78 748)